KISHANI SENEVIRATNE

UX/UI & VISUAL DESIGN

CALL: 323 394 9116
EMAIL: write.kish@gmail.com

10+ years as a design professional. Art director with experience working for top-tier advertising and marketing agencies delivering innovative solutions for leading financial, beauty, technology and pharmaceutical clients, and 5+ years as a freelance visual designer for small agencies catering to the entertainment, publishing, restaurant and automotive industries.

SKILLS:

- Expertise in all channels, specializing in branding and concepting for campaigns, web sites, banners, emails, and social media.
- Strong communication skills in client management and collaborations with developers, other creatives, and account team members.
- Reliable and committed to follow-through, organized, energetic and team-oriented, meeting deadlines and delivering compelling
 pieces for a variety of audiences.

WORK EXPERIENCE:

Art Director/Designer

Freelance

July 2011 - Present

Created web sites, digital and print advertising campaigns, email campaigns, mobile apps, and printed promotional materials. Partnered with clients to manage budgets and timelines. Communicated with international vendors to ensure prompt and efficient printing of advertising materials.

CLIENTS: Joe and the Juice, Elsevier Publishing, Amgen, CVS/Pharmacy, Elsevier, ZocDoc, Scholastic, TGIFridays Restaurants and National Education Association

AGENCIES: Digitas Health, Havas, DUPO, BCG Digital Ventures and Meredith Xcelerated Marketing

Senior Art Director Digitas/Digitas Health

Nov 2006 – July 2011

Designed and produced web sites, online advertising campaigns, ad banners, email campaigns, mobile applications, online video campaigns and a television spot for clients in the pharmaceutical industry. Led small teams including UX designers, production artists and developers on multiple projects.

Concepted assignments, pitched presentations and completed projects for IBM.com including new site sections, site enhancements and microsites. Presented creative concepts to internal creative and account groups as well as clients.

CLIENTS: IBM, Samsung, TIAA-CREF and HSBC, Bristol-Myers Squibb and Pfizer

Art Director

...and company 2004 - 2006

Art Director

Freelance 2001 – 2004

Designer Envision Group 2000 – 2001 **CLIENTS:** William Morris Agency, Bravo, CBS, USA, HBO Independent, and Mattel

CLIENTS: Greentree, Redmond Group and Kemp Group

CLIENTS: Neutrogena and Isuzu Motors

EDUCATION:

California State University, Long Beach BFA, Graphic Design

UX/UI Boot Camp, UC Irvine

SKILLS & TOOLS:

Sketch Adobe CS5 Invision Principle MS Office

PORTFOLIO:

kishaniseneviratne.com Password: yeah!

LINKEDIN PROFILE:

https://www.linkedin.com/in/kishani/